💞 kissasian.one 💞
💞 kissasian.one 💞
Hello, Brother, what's wrong?
Ciao, fratello. Che c'è?
Sis, has the seal been broken?
Jie, il sigillo si è spezzato?
Broken?
Spezzato?
I had a fever after I came back yesterday.
Ho la febbre da ieri.
And then today, I started to hear some strange noises whispering in my ears.
E poi oggi, ho iniziato a sentire strani rumori e sussurri.
Also, my protective amulet is broken.
E il mio amuleto protettivo si è rotto.
Buxia, did you say you can hear them now?
Buxia, hai detto che li senti?
Just calm down first.
Adesso calmati.
Grandpa said whoever takes over the temple has to be responsible for it.
Il nonno ha detto che chiunque prenda il controllo del tempio deve esserne responsabile.
We all know you're scared, so I volunteered to do it.
Sappiamo tutti che hai paura, per quello mi sono offerta.
I burned my talisman last night.
Ieri sera ho bruciato il mio talismano.
Now, I can hear, see, and talk to them.
Ora, riesco a sentirli, vederli e parlare con loro.
And?
E quindi?
You burned yours, but mine's still sealed.
Hai bruciato il tuo, ma il mio sigillo è ancora intatto.
Didn't Senior help strengthen my seal?
Senior non ti ha aiutato a potenziarlo?
I burned my talisman to unseal it,
Ho bruciato il mio talismano per aprirlo,
- but... - But what? Be more specific.
- però… - Però cosa? Sii più specifica.
I accidentally burned a tiny part of yours.
Per errore ho bruciato un pezzetto del tuo.
Really just a little bit.
Davvero minuscolo.
I thought it wouldn't cause any major problems.
Ho pensato che non potesse causare grossi problemi.
Anyway, just hang in there for now.
Comunque, ora mettiamo giù.
Pretend like you're listening to ghost stories in a podcast.
Fai finta di sentire storie di fantasmi da un podcast.
At least you can only hear them and not see them right now.
Almeno li senti, ma non li vedi.
I will figure something out.
Troverò una soluzione.
Wait for me.
Aspetta.
I'm so cold.
Che freddo.
So cold.
Fa freddissimo!
I want to redress my grievances. I want revenge.
Voglio rimediare alle mie ingiustizie. Voglio vendetta!
[Newton and the Apple]
[Newton e la mela]
♫ When I think of you ♫
♫ Quando penso a te ♫
♫ I think about the first time we met ♫
♫ Mi viene in mente la prima volta che ti ho visto ♫
♫ Suddenly my heart flipped ♫
♫ All'improvviso il mio cuore ha sussultato ♫
♫ And I fall into the life of a drama play ♫
♫ E sono finito nella vita di un drama ♫
♫ You're Newton and I'm the apple ♫
♫ Tu sei Newton e io la mela ♫
♫ Falling from the tree ♫
♫ Che cade dall'albero ♫
♫ Oh, take a bite ♫
♫ Oh, dai un morso ♫
♫ Just like fish needs water ♫
♫ Proprio come i pesci hanno bisogno dell'acqua ♫
♫ You're summer and I'm the breeze ♫
♫ Tu sei l'estate e io la brezza ♫
♫ Blowing from the sea ♫
♫ Che soffia dal mare ♫
♫ I don't understand why love always makes people feel at a loss ♫
♫ Non capisco perché l'amore ci fa sempre sentire in difficoltà ♫
[Stay by My Side]
💕 Stay by My Side 👻
[Episode 3: Getting Closer, And Then What?]
Episodio 3: Avvicinarsi e poi? 👻
Please. I'm going crazy just hearing it.
Ti prego. Impazzisco solo a sentirli.
Please don't let me see it.
Ti scongiuro non farmeli vedere.
Save me. There's a ghost.
Salvami. C'è un fantasma.
Why are you hiding here to scare me?
Perché ti nascondi per spaventarmi?
You're the ghost, aren't you?
Sei un fantasma?
Help!
Aiuto!
Can you tell me your birth date and time?
Puoi dirmi quando sei nato e a che ora?
It's okay if you don't want to say it.
Non importa se non vuoi dirlo.
Just tell me how heavy your 'Eight Characters' are.
Mi basta sapere i tuoi "otto caratteri".
Those sounds... Strange.
Quei suoni… che strano.
When I touched him, those sounds disappear.
Quando lo tocca, spariscono.
Why does it have to be him?
Perché proprio lui?
He must think I'm crazy.
Deve pensare che io sia pazzo.
If I were him,
Se fossi in lui,
I'd probably kick me out.
mi caccerei a pedate.
You said it gets cold when the ghost sounds appear,
Hai detto che fa freddo quando senti i fantasmi,
but when you touched your roommate, the sounds disappeared and it got warm.
ma se tocchi il tuo compagno di stanza, i suoni spariscono e torna a far caldo.
I've tried a few times, and it seems to be true.
Ci ho provato un paio di volte e sembra essere così.
How heavy are his 'Eight Characters'?
Quanto pesato i suoi "otto caratteri"?
I asked him, but he just looked at me like I was crazy.
Gliel'ho chiesto, ma mi ha guardato come se fossi pazzo.
You should try a few more times to see the effect.
Dovresti provare ancora un paio di volte se funziona.
This makes me look like a pervert.
Mi fa sembrare un maniaco.
All right. I'll find a chance to try again.
Va bene. Troverò il modo di riprovarci.
Luckily, I only burned a corner of it.
Per fortuna, ho bruciato solo un angolo del talismano.
To prevent you from seeing what you shouldn't,
Per evitare di vedere ciò che non dovresti…
just stick close to your roommate for now.
resta attaccato al tuo compagno di stanza.
Sis, you made this mess,
Jie, hai fatto questo casino,
hurry up and fix it.
sbrigati a sistemarlo.
Sis.
Jie.
This is for you to give to Jiang Chi.
Questo lo devi dare a Jiang Chi.
You can't eat it yourself.
Non puoi mangiarlo da solo.
You haven't touched the money in your account.
Non hai toccato i soldi sul tuo conto.
How did you register?
Come hai fatto a iscriverti?
Don't worry about me.
Non preoccuparti per me.
I won't do anything illegal.
Non farò nulla di illegale.
You won't lose face.
Non perderai la reputazione.
How much can you make by working part-time?
Quanto guadagni con un lavoro part time?
Delivery, courier, and dishwashing?
Consegne, corriere e lavapiatti?
You followed me?
Mi hai seguito?
You watch too many TV dramas.
Vedi troppi drama.
People might think I did something wrong.
La gente potrebbe pensare che ho fatto qualcosa di male.
What's wrong with being a doctor? Why study law?
Che male c'è a diventare medico? Perché studiare legge?
Your brother and sister are already capable on their own.
Tuo fratello e tua sorella se la cavano già da soli.
Isn't that enough?
Non è abbastanza?
If you have medical disputes in the future, I won't charge you.
Se in futuro avrai controversie mediche, non ti farò pagare.
Actually, he's quite cute when he's not being sarcastic.
A ben vedere, è carino quando non fa il sarcastico.
Not as cute as me though.
Non quanto me, però.
No wonder some people will give him snacks, but not me.
Ecco perché la gente gli dà da mangiare.
What?
Che c'è?
Why would you scare people with your small courage?
Perché spaventi la gente se sei un fifone?
You're the one with small courage.
Sei tu il fifone.
I wanted to surprise you.
Volevo farti una sorpresa.
It's rare to meet you when you're not on your way to work or class.
È difficile incontrarti quando non vai al lavoro o a lezione.
This is for you.
Questo è per te.
A female classmate asked me to give it to you.
Una ragazza mi ha chiesto di dartelo.
It's not from me.
Non è da parte mia.
I don't want it.
Non lo voglio.
If you don't want it, then I'll eat it.
Se non lo vuoi, allora lo mangio io.
It's a nice gift from a girl.
È un bel regalo da parte di una ragazza.
Just accept it with gratitude.
Accettalo e ringrazia.
I don't want to be misunderstood.
Non voglio che fraintenda.
Then I'll really eat it.
Allora lo mangio io per davvero.
♫ When I'm lonely, I will vigorously count the unhurried fingertips ♫
♫ Quando sarò solo, conterò sulle dita senza fretta ♫
♫ I'm stupid crazy... ♫
♫ Sono un pazzo… ♫
Translating English to Chinese, huh?
Traduci dall'inglese al cinese?
Are you doing a new part-time job or just reading?
È un nuovo lavoro o leggi e basta?
♫ The eager heart throbs ♫
♫ Il cuore impaziente pulsa ♫
♫ This habit is yours is a unique little action ♫
♫ Questa tua abitudine è unica ♫
♫ Falling like rain ♫
♫ Cade come la pioggia ♫
My sister always says I have a loose mouth.
Mia sorella dice sempre che parlo troppo.
You can go back to work. Don't mind me.
Torna al lavoro. Non fare caso a me.
♫ You're summer and I'm the breeze ♫
♫ Tu sei l'estate e io la brezza ♫
♫ Blowing from the sea ♫
♫ Che soffia dal mare ♫
♫ I don't understand why love always makes people feel at a loss ♫
♫ Non capisco perché l'amore ci fa sempre sentire in difficoltà ♫
How can he appear so unexpectedly,
Come ha fatto ad apparire all'improvviso,
and get close so naturally?
ed essersi avvicinato in modo naturale?
Why?
Perché?
[Ask: Who are these two?]
[Chi sono loro due?]
[I'm from the drama department.] [Saw them both at noon] [Isn't this Jiang Chi from the law department?]
[Sono del dipartimento di recitazione] [Li ho visti a mezzogiorno] [Non è Jiang Chi di legge?]
[That is Gu Buxia from the anthropology department!] [I want to film them.  Please advise]
[È Gu Buxia di antropologia!] [Vorrei fargli un video. Avvisatemi]
[Prophecy, are 404 together?] [Upstairs, don't let two men be together]
[Profezia, 404 sono insieme?] [Due uomini non possono stare insieme]
[Ah~ that's my dessert]
[Ah~ quello è il mio dolce]
[Why did Gu Buxia still eat it?] [Jiang Chi watched, he ate] [I think it's okay]
[Perché lo mangia Gu Buxia?] [Jiang Chi ha guardato lui che lo mangiava] [Penso vada bene]
[Upstairs, please abdicate!] [Contribute more photos] [Classmate Gu can smile and it repels Classmate Jiang]
[Rinunciaci, per favore!] [Mandate altre foto] [Gu sorride e respinge Jiang]
[Ah, this angle, please tell me.  Did they kiss?]
[Ah, questa angolatura. Si sono baciati?]
[Did the two have a relationship before?] [What kind of cheap trick is this? How could Jiang Chi lose?]
[Stavano con qualcun altro prima?] [Non è possibile. Come fa Jiang Chi a perdere?]
[404CP "Standalone" Is there anyone else who wants to follow?]
[404CP "Indipendente" Qualcun altro vuole seguire?]
I'm glad you're here.
Che bello che sei qui.
A hug with you gives me a quiet moment.
Un tuo abbraccio mi dà un attimo di tregua.
A good deal.
È un ottimo affare.
What are you doing?
Che fai?
[A. No loud talking, B. Table and Chairs should be put back in place after use, C. Keep the environment clean and tidy. THANKS!!]
[A. Non si parla a voce alta. | B. Tavoli e sedie vanno rimessi a posto. | C. Tenere pulito e ordinato. Grazie!!]
Does it only happen when you're close to Jiang Chi?
Succede solo quando sei vicino a Jiang Chi?
Do you want to try with someone else?
Vuoi provare con qualcun altro?
Otherwise, what if he disappears?
Perché… se sparisse?
That's too impressive.
Incredibile.
How is it? Does it look like a poster?
Com'è? Sembra un poster?
Gathering in the morning,
Vi vedete di mattina…
- what are you looking at? - I miss it so much.
- cosa guardate? - Mi manca tanto.
- Looking at some collected photos. - I used to...
- Guardiamo delle foto… - Una volta avevo…
- Watching you guys interact. - have such photos as well.
- …di voi ragazzi che interagite. - anche io tante foto.
Getting along so well is nice.
Andare tutti d'accordo è così bello.
What's this?
Che cos'è?
- What do you think of this set of photos? - Too close.
- Che ne pensi delle foto? - È troppo vicino.
- Cool, right? - Perhaps he...
- Belle, vero? - Forse…
- Everyone likes them a lot. - can't hear.
- Piacciono a tutti. - non riesce a sentire.
This guy Jiang is so full of positive energy.
Jiang è così pieno di energia positiva.
Should we think of a way to drive him away?
Troviamo un modo per mandarlo via?
- What are all these? - Jiang. Gu.
- Cosa sono? - Jiang. Gu.
These two are so close again.
Sono di nuovo così vicini.
This can't be.
Non può essere.
You're really special to me.
Sei davvero speciale per me.
♫ Because I know you too well, my dear ♫
♫ Perché ti conosco troppo bene, mio caro ♫
♫ What you didn't say, let me tell you first ♫
♫ Quello che non hai detto, te lo dico io ♫
How did I just hug him like that?
Perché l'ho abbracciato così?
What if he thinks I want to try something?
E se pensasse che ho secondi fini?
What do you mean by that?
Che cosa significa?
What do you mean?
Che cosa?
You said I'm special to you. How special?
Hai detto che sono speciale per te. In che senso?
Why is that?
Che vuol dire?
Can you not get so close to me so casually?
Ti avvicini così come se niente fosse?
Jiang Chi, wait a moment.
Jiang Chi, aspetta.
What's up?
Che c'è?
About joining the basketball team, do you really not want to reconsider?
Non vuoi proprio unirti alla squadra di basket?
I told you, I don't have the time.
Te l'ho detto, non ho tempo.
I thought since you live with Buxia,
Ho pensato che, siccome vivi  con Buxia,
you two should have a tacit understanding.
avete un tacito accordo.
Are you close to him?
Sei sua amica?
Of course. Our team is like a family.
Certo. La nostra squadra è come una famiglia.
Can I ask you a question?
Posso farti una domanda?
As long as it's about the basketball team, you can ask me.
Se riguarda la squadra, chiedi pure.
It's a personal question.
È una domanda personale.
I have a friend, who's always being harassed by someone in various ways.
Ho un amico, che viene spesso assillato da qualcuno in modi diversi.
He finds all kinds of reasons to be around him,
Trova tutti i modi per stargli attorno,
often stares at him,
spesso lo fissa,
and even touches him intentionally or unintentionally.
e lo tocca anche di proposito e non.
Didn't your friend fight him back?
Il tuo amico lo colpisce di rimando?
Then it's not harassment.
Allora non è un'aggressione.
It should be considered
Dovrebbe essere…
body language that shows affection.
un linguaggio del corpo che dimostra affetto.
Besides physical contact, did he say anything else?
A parte il contatto fisico, ha detto altro?
He said that he was very special.
Gli ha detto che era molto speciale.
Then I get it.
Allora ho capito.
Affection at first sight, wanting to stay together,
Affetto appena lo vede, vuole stargli sempre accanto,
it's the special person in one's life.
è una persona speciale per lui.
Just wait a little longer.
Aspetta ancora un po'…
He will start to play hard to get,
Comincerà a fare il difficile
waiting for someone to confess first.
per vedere chi dei due si dichiarerà per primo.
Where did a confession come from?
E da dove arriva questa idea?
Who is that friend of yours?
Chi è questo tuo amico?
Why not just ask him out for a chat?
Perché non gli chiedi di parlare?
I have a class now. I'll leave first.
Ho lezione. Devo andare.
Jiang Chi, please consider joining the basketball team again.
Jiang Chi, per favore, ripensaci per la squadra di basket.
[Yong Yu Gymnasium]
[Palestra Yong Yu]
For the Interschool Cup second-round knockout match,
Per l'incontro del secondo turno della Coppa Interscolastica,
since the opponent forfeited, we're confirmed to advance.
dato che gli avversari hanno dato forfait, avanzeremo noi.
Why are you so excited about advancing by forfeit?
Cosa c'è di bello a vincere per abbandono degli altri?
Why don't we just forfeit, too?
Diamo forfait anche noi?
It will be an early relief.
Sarebbe un sollievo.
So that we don't embarrass ourselves.
Almeno non ci metteremo in imbarazzo.
Don't be so negative.
Non essere così negativo.
Like I told you, I'm here.
Come ti ho detto, io sono qui.
Can you play against five people on your own?
Puoi giocare da solo contro cinque?
My leg is injured, so I can't keep up with you.
Ho la gamba infortunata, non riesco a tenere il tuo ritmo.
Yunhao isn't accurate enough. Baiwei isn't fast enough.
Yunhao non è preciso. Baiwei non è veloce.
Others either lack experience or have poor stamina.
Agli altri manca esperienza e resistenza.
I heard that the captain and team manager tried to recruit Jiang Chi.
Ho sentito che la team manager e il capitano stanno cercando di reclutare Jiang Chi.
- And then? - Rejected in a second. It's up to you.
- E quindi? - Ha rifiutato. Devi farlo tu.
Me?
Io?
You haven't answered my question from this morning.
Non hai risposto alla mia domanda di stamattina.
Wow!
Cavolo!
Your feelings are heating up quickly.
Vi siete scaldati in fretta.
What were you two whispering about just now?
Cosa vi stavate sussurrando?
He did it on purpose.
L'ha fatto apposta.
On purpose. On what purpose?
Apposta? Che cosa?
Intentionally making everyone think you two get along well.
Per farci credere che andate d'accordo?
Please, he's Jiang Chi.
Per favore, è Jiang Chi.
The famous Ice Cube Man of the law department.
Il famoso Uomo di Ghiaccio di legge.
He's not idle. Right?
Non batte la fiacca. Giusto?
You're responsible for bringing him in.
Sei responsabile per farlo entrare in squadra.
You don't even know if he can play basketball.
Non sapete nemmeno se sa giocare.
He's not taller than me, and his attitude isn't better than mine.
Non è più alto di me e non ha un atteggiamento migliore del mio.
He just looks a little cooler holding a basketball.
È solo un po' più figo quando tiene la palla da basket.
If you don't bring him in, you don't need to play in the next match.
Se non lo porti qui, non giocherai nella prossima partita.
I...
Io…
[Select Cases of American Law]
[Casi di Diritto Americano]
Blackmail? Bribe? Begging?
Ricatto? Corruzione? Supplica?
If he ignores me, the captain really won't let me play.
Se mi ignora, il capitano non mi farà giocare.
If you turn it on, watch it.
Se la accendi, guardala.
And if you aren't watching, turn it off.
Altrimenti, spegnila.
Do you have anything to say to your special person?
Hai qualcosa da dire alla tua persona speciale?
Can you stop staring at me like this?
Puoi smetterla di guardarmi così?
If you weren't staring at me,
Se non mi guardavi tu,
you wouldn't notice my looking at you.
non ti saresti accorto di me.
The last time we arm wrestled,
Quando abbiamo fatto braccio di ferro,
you were so close to me and not embarrassed.
eri vicinissimo a me e non eri in imbarazzo.
How come now when I get close to you, you immediately turn away?
Come mai adesso quando mi avvicino, ti giri immediatamente?
You were the one who came close, and you're the one who's dodging.
Sei tu che ti sei avvicinato e ora sei quello che si scosta.
Aren't you going to explain?
Hai intenzione di spiegarmi?
Tell me. What do you want with me?
Avanti. Che cosa vuoi da me?
Actually, our fates are interestingly tied.
In realtà, i nostri destini sono legati.
We met at the school gate. Do you remember?
Ci siamo incontrati ai cancelli di ingresso. Ti ricordi?
I almost bumped into you like this.
Mi sono quasi imbattuto in te così.
Later, on the basketball court, you caught my pass
Poi, al campo da basket, hai preso la mia palla
and made a nice shoot.
e hai fatto canestro.
💞 kissasian.one 💞
Sincronizzazione e sottotitoli offerti dal Ghosts and Lovers 👻❤️ Team @Viki.com
That's right. I find it very comfortable being with you.
È vero. Sono molto a mio agio quando sono con te.
But you're so busy, and we don't have classes in the same department.
Ma tu sei impegnato e non abbiamo lezioni in comune.
So I thought... do you have time to join the basketball team?
Così ho pensato… hai tempo di unirti alla squadra di basket?
That way, we'd have more chances to interact.
Così, avremo modo di interagire di più.
And more opportunities to get to know each other.
E avremo più opportunità di conoscerci.
You find it comfortable being with me,
Ti senti a tuo agio con me.
and you want to spend more time with me.
E vuoi trascorrere più tempo con me.
So you got close to me just to get me to join the basketball team?
Quindi ti sei avvicinato per farmi unire alla squadra di basket?
No.
No.
Mainly I want to have more time to be with you,
Più che altro perché voglio avere più tempo per stare con te,
and the basketball team needs you too.
e servi anche alla squadra.
Also, the basketball team offers subsidies.
E poi, la squadra di basket offre sussidi.
You need money, don't you?
Ti servono i soldi, no?
What do you think?
Che ne dici?
You mentioned so many benefits of joining the basketball team.
Hai elencato un sacco di benefici.
If I spend so much time with you, what's in it for me?
Se trascorro più tempo con te, cosa ci guadagno?
Spending time with me?
Più tempo con me?
You're spending time with me?
Vuoi trascorrere più tempo con me?
If I'm so special to you, let's see your actions.
Se sono speciale per te, vediamo come ti comporti.
♫ My vision has run wild and my hearing is wrong, and I even laugh unconsciously ♫
♫ La mia vista si scatena e il mio udito si sbaglia e rido senza rendermene conto ♫
♫ I block all messages from the world, and you're the only frequency I receive ♫
♫ Blocco i messaggi del mondo e sei l'unica frequenza che percepisco ♫
♫ How to unlock the clues? Where is the exit? ♫
♫ Come sblocco gli indizi? Dov'è l'uscita? ♫
♫ I wash my hands, rinse my eyes, you haunt me in my dreams ♫
♫ Qualunque cosa faccia, appari nei miei sogni ♫
♫ You and I hold hands tightly (hold tightly), striding (never missing out) ♫
♫ Teniamoci per mano e camminiamo insieme ♫
♫ My chest is broad for you ♫
♫ Il mio petto si gonfia per te ♫
♫ Don't leave me stranded in a sea of people ♫
♫ Non lasciarmi bloccato tra la folla ♫
♫ Crying for help on an island of memories ♫
♫ Mentre chiedo aiuto su un'isola di ricordi ♫
♫ I don't want anyone to find out ♫
♫ Non voglio che qualcuno lo scopra ♫
♫ But just want you to hear me ♫
♫ Voglio solo che mi ascolti ♫
♫ I miss you ♫
♫ Mi manchi ♫
♫ Like a wildfire ♫
♫ Come un incendio ♫
♫ Breaking taboos and boundaries ♫
♫ Distruggi i tabù e i confini ♫
♫ Spreading endlessly ♫
♫ Ti espandi senza fine ♫
♫ Did you hear that? ♫
♫ L'hai sentito? ♫
♫ I finally understand ♫
♫ Finalmente capisco ♫
♫ The words I never said to you ♫
♫ Le parole che non ti ho detto ♫
♫ Please answer me if you can hear me ♫
♫ Per favore, se mi senti, rispondimi ♫
♫ Okay? ♫
♫ Va bene? ♫
💞 kissasian.one 💞
💞 kissasian.one 💞
Are you asking me when I'll be back because you miss me?
Anteprima 👻 Vuoi sapere quando torno perché ti manco?
You study medicine and law, so you won't believe in these things.
Studi legge e medicina, quindi non crederai a queste cose.
I'm always here if you need me.
Ci sono sempre se hai bisogno di me.
You can actually smile like that at others, but only give me a poker face.
Agli altri sorridi così, mentre a me fai sempre vedere quel broncio.
You're really kind to your classmates.
Sei gentile con i tuoi compagni di classe.
I don't do it for others. And there's no need to.
Non lo faccio per gli altri. E non ce n'è bisogno.
Actually, I really do like you a lot.
In realtà, mi piaci molto.